(Leonard:)Fine. Just get back under your blanket
and I'll drive you there.
(Sheldon:)And no more singing.
(Leonard:)Fine.
l have GPS on my phone.
I know you turned around.
(Penny:)I'm so glad you talked Howard...
(Penny:)...out of having your wedding invitations
in Klingon.
(Bernadette:)Turn it over.
(Bernadette:)I'm hoping my relatives
think it's Hebrew.
(Amy:)This is really happening.
I'm gonna be a maid of honor.
'I'm gonna wear a beautiful dress
and walk down that aisle...
(Amy:)...and finally,
I will have my special day.
(Bernadette:)You mean my special day.
(Amy:)They're gonna need an extra-large veil
for somebody's head.
- If I actually ever get married.
- Why wouldn't you?
(Bernadette:)My dad. Because I make
a lot more money than Howie...